- I got him!
- Take him down!
- 超过他了!
- 打败他!
- He's got you, sheldon.
- Look at this move!
- 他超过你了 Sheldon
- 瞧这下!
He's completely schooling you.
他完全超过你了
Hey, guys, guys, some of the other
waitresses wanted me to ask you something.
嘿 伙计们 伙计们
别的女服务生要我问你们点事
It's called tressling.
这叫Tressling
It combines the physical strength of arm
wrestling with the mental agility of tetris
是一项将掰手腕的体力和
玩俄罗斯方块的
into the ultimate sport.
思维能力集为一体的运动
Yeah, that's terrific, but what they wanted
me to ask you is to cut it the hell out.
嗯 听起来很厉害
但是她们叫你们快别玩了
Great. Come here, guys. Come on.
很好 来吧 伙计们 来吧
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐
we might as well stop. It's a stalemate.
我们最好停下吧 陷入平局了
You're beating me in tetris, but you've got
the upper body strength of a keebler elf.
俄罗斯方块上你赢了我
但你的上肢力量就像Keebler饼干玩偶
Keebler elf? I've got your
keebler elf right here.
Keebler玩偶?
让你瞧瞧Keebler玩偶的厉害
okay, it's a stalemate.
好吧 平局
So, leonard, will we be seeing you on
saturday for your free birthday cheesecake?
那么 Leonard
周六带免费芝士蛋糕去见你?
He can't eat cheesecake.
He's lactose intolerant.
他不能吃芝士蛋糕 他不吃乳糖的
Okay, he can have carrot cake.
好吧 他可以吃胡萝卜蛋糕
What about the cream cheese frosting?
那层奶油干酪怎么办?
He can scrape it off.
可以刮掉嘛
Forget about the cake. How do you
know that my birthday's saturday?
别管蛋糕了 你怎么知道周六是我生日?
I did your horoscope, remember?
我帮你算过星座 记得不?
I was going to do everybody's, until sheldon
went on one of his typical psychotic rants.
我本来要帮所有人算的
但Sheldon开始了他的疯言疯语
For the record, "that psychotic rant"
请注意 你所谓的"疯言疯语"
was a concise summation of
the research of bertram forer,
是巴纳姆效应的简明总结
who, in 1948, proved conclusively
through meticulously designed experiments
他在1948年经过精密的设计性实验得出
that astrology is nothing
but pseudo-scientific hokum.
占星学只不过是一堆伪科学的废话
Blah, blah, blah. Typical taurus.
废话好多 典型的金牛座
So, seriously, are we
going to see you saturday?
说真的 我们周六能见到你吗?
Uh, I don't think so.
呃 我不这么认为
Why not?
为什么不?
I don't celebrate my birthday.
我不庆祝生日的
Shut up. Yeah, you do.
少来 咋会不庆祝呢
It's no big deal; it's
just the way I was raised.
就是普通日子嘛 我就这么长大的
My parents focused on
celebrating achievements,
我父母注重于庆祝巨大成就
and being expelled from a birth
canal was not considered one of them.
我从产道里蹦出来对他们来说
并不是什么成就
that's so silly.
这太愚蠢了
Sheldon: It's actually
based on very sound theories.
实际上这基于非常有力的理论
His mother published a paper on it.
他母亲还就此发表了论文
Well, what was it called?
哦? 叫什么题目?
"I hate my son and that's
why he can't have cake"?
"我讨厌我儿子 所以他不能吃蛋糕"?
Sheldon: It was obviously effective.
这样做显然很有效果
Leonard grew up to be an
experimental physicist.
Leonard长大成为一个实验物理学家
Perhaps if she'd also denied him
christmas, he'd be a little better at it.
也许 如果她也不让他过圣诞节
他就会比现在更优秀
Thank you.
谢谢你
Well, I love birthdays.
我喜欢过生日
Waking up to mom's special
french toast breakfast,
早上起来吃妈妈特制的法国吐司
wearing the birthday king crown,
playing laser tag with all my friends...
头戴生日王冠
和所有的朋友一起玩激光搏击...
yeah, see? That's what kids should have.
是啊 瞧见没? 孩子就应该这么过
Actually, that was last year.
实际上 说的是我去年的生日
So you really never
had a birthday party?
你真的 从来没有 办过生日派对?
No, but it was okay.
没有 不过没关系
I mean, when I was little,
我是指 在我还小的时候
I'd think maybe my parents would change
their mind and surprise me with a party.
我曾想也许我父母会改变主意
然后给我一个惊喜派对
Like this one birthday I
came home from my cello lesson
比如有次生日 我刚学完大提琴回家
and I saw a lot of strange
cars parked out front.
我看到很多陌生车停在门外
When I got to the door, I
could hear people whispering
走到门口 还听见人们在小声说话
and I could smell german chocolate
cake, which is my favorite.
而且还闻到了德国巧克力蛋糕的味道
那是我最喜欢的蛋糕
And?
然后呢?
It turns out my grandfather had died.
结果是我爷爷去世了
Oh, my god. That's terrible.
噢 我的天哪 这太恐怖了
Well, it was kind of
like a birthday party.
但我觉得也算个生日派对了
I got to see all my cousins,
and there was cake, so...
我见到了所有的表兄弟 也有蛋糕 所以...
that's the saddest
thing I've ever heard.
这是我听过最可怜的事了
You think?
你这么觉得?
Go ahead, tell her
about your senior prom.
来吧 告诉她你的毕业舞会
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: lauracai 王泳东 MiaT
校对: 欧屁屁
时间轴: 咔肉肉
The Big Bang Theory
Season01 Episode16
天才理论传
第一季 第16集
********Remember--
no peanuts.
一定要记得--不要放花生
Howard, every thai restaurant in
town knows you can't eat peanuts.
Howard 城里每个泰国餐厅
都知道你不能吃花生
When they see me coming,
they go, "ah, no-peanut boy!"
他们一看到我去
就会说"啊 不要花生的男孩!"
Hello, penny. Leonard just left.
你好 Penny
Leonard刚刚出门
I know. I want to talk to you.
我知道 我想要跟你谈谈
What would we talk about?
我们谈些什么?
We have no overlapping areas
of interest I'm aware of.
我想 我们还没发现兴趣的交集
As you know, I don't care for chitchat.
你知道的 我不喜欢闲谈
Can you just let me in?
能让我进去吗?
Well, all right, but I don't
see this as a promising endeavor.
好吧 但我不觉得这招管用
Okay, here's the deal.
好吧 事情是这样的
We are going to throw leonard a kick-ass
surprise party for his birthday on saturday.
我们周六给Leonard办个
超惊喜的生日派对
I hardly think so.
我很难同意
Leonard made it very clear
he doesn't want a party.
Leonard说的很清楚 他不要派对
Did someone say... "party"?
刚才有人说..."派对"?
He just doesn't know he wants
one 'cause he's never had one.
他并不知道自己想要
因为他从没有过生日派对
I suppose that's possible,
but for the record,
就算是的 但请注意
I've never had a threesome and
yet I still know I want one.
我从没玩过3P 但我知道我想要
Howard, here's
the difference--
Howard 这两者的区别是--
the possibility exists that leonard could
have a birthday party before hell freezes over.
在地狱结冰之前
Leonard过生日派对存在可能性
Fine. If I do have a threesome,
you can't be part of it.
好吧 如果我真的玩3P 你不能参加
I'm just kidding. Yes, you can.
我开玩笑的 你当然能参加了
Can you bring a friend?
能再带个朋友吗?
I think a birthday
party's a terrible idea.
我觉得生日派对是个糟糕的想法
I envy leonard for growing
up without that anguish.
我很羡慕Leonard
成长过程中没有这种痛苦
Anguish?
痛苦?
Year after year, I had to
endure wearing comical hats
年复一年 我必须强忍戴上滑稽的帽子
while being forced into the crowded,
sweaty hell of bouncy castles.
被迫挤在人群中 弄得满身大汗
Not to mention being blindfolded and being
spun toward a grotesque tailless donkey
更别提要被蒙上眼睛
转着走向那头硕大的无尾驴
as the other children
mocked my disorientation.
走错了方向 更要被其他孩子嘲笑
Okay, sweetie, I understand you have
scars that no nonprofessional can heal,
好吧 亲爱的 我知道你心里的伤
一般人治不了
but, nevertheless, we're going
to throw leonard a birthday party.
但我们仍旧要给Leonard办个生日派对
Have I pointed out that I'm
extremely uncomfortable with dancing,
我说过吗? 我极度地不喜欢跳舞
loud music and most other forms
of alcohol-induced frivolity?
还包括吵闹的音乐
以及大多数人在酒后的轻佻行为
Nevertheless, we're...
虽然如此 我们...
- in addition, I really don't think that leonard wants...
- okay, here's the deal:
- 而且 我觉得Leonard才不会希望...
- 好吧 这样如何:
You either you help me throw leonard
a birthday party or, so help me god,
你要么帮我给Leonard
办一个生日派对 否则
I will go in youour droom and unbag all of
your most valuable, mint-condition comic books.
我会到你的卧室里把你最珍贵的
完好无损的漫画书统统倒出
And on one of them-- t u won'yoknow
which-- I'll draw a tiny happy face in ink.
在其中任选你不知道的一页--
用墨水在上面画个迷你笑脸
You can't do that. If you make a mark in
a mint comic book, it's no longer mint.
你不能那么干 你在完好无损的书上
做记号 那就不再是完好无损了
Sheldon, do you understand
the concept of blackmail?
Sheldon 你脑里有勒索这个概念吗?
Well, of course, I... oh.
当然 我...噢
Yeah, I have an idea.
对 我有办法了
Let's throw leonard a
kick-ass birthday party.
我们给Leonard办个
超赞的生日派对
that's not the secret knock.
暗号不对
This is the secret knock.
看我的正确演示
what difference does it make?
有什么不同的效果呢?
The whole point of a secret knock
is to establish a non-verbal signal
暗号的精髓就在于
建立一种非言语的暗号
to verify the identity
of one's co-conspirators.
用于查证同谋们的身份
Penny: Is that raj and howard?
是Raj和Howard?
Possibly, but unverified.
有可能 查证中
Will you just let us in.
还打算让我们进去吗
Luckily for you, this
is not a nuclear reactor.
你们很幸运
我们不是在搞核反应堆
So what'd you get the birthday boy?
你们给寿星准备了什么呢?
Well, raj got him an awesome,
limited edition dark knight sculpture
Raj给他准备的是限定版的
黑暗骑士人偶 非常之棒
based on alex ross's definitive batman.
按照AlexRoss's诠释的
终极蝙蝠侠
And I got him this amazing autographed
copy of the feynman lectures on physics.
我给他准备的是费曼物理学讲义
题署本 绝对让人惊喜
Nice. I got him a sweater.
不错嘛 我准备的是一件毛衣
Okay, well, he might like
that. I've seen him get chilly.
他可能会喜欢的
我见他有些怕冷
Sheldon, I didn't see your present.
Sheldon我还没有看到你的礼物呢
That's because I didn't bring one.
因为我根本没准备
- Why not?
- Don't ask.
- 为什么?
- 别问他
The entire institution of
gift-giving makes no sense.
整个俗世的礼尚往来完全没有意义
Too late.
又晚了一步
Let's say I go out
and I spend $50 on you.
如果说我出门然后为了花上50美元
It's a laborious activity because
I have to imagine what you need,
这活动很费劲 因为我得想着
你需要什么呢
whereas you know what you need.
实际上你自己最清楚你需要什么
Now, I could simplify things--
just give you the $50 directly,
那么 我何不将事情简单化--
直接给你50美元不就行了
and then you could give
me $50 on my birthday,
今后我的生日
你也可以送我50美元嘛
and so on, until one of us dies,
leaving the other one old and $50 richer.
如此礼尚往来 直到有个人离开人世
丢下另外一个多50美元钱的老人
And I ask you, is it worth it?
请问 这样做有意义吗?
Told you not to ask.
说了不要问的嘛
Well, sheldon, you're his friend.
Sheldon 你可是他的朋友呀
Friends give each other presents.
朋友们就该是互赠礼物的呀
I accept your premise;
I reject your conclusion.
我同意你的提论
但不认同你的结论
Try telling him it's a
non-optional social convention.
试试让他明白这是
不依个人意志的社交惯例吧
- What?
- Just do it.
- 什么?
- 照做就是了
it's a non-optional...
social convention.
这是不依个人意志的...
社交惯例
Fair enough.
说的有道理
He came with a manual.
他嘛 有随机附送的使用手册
Question-- how am I going to get
leonard a present before the party?
提问--我怎样才能在派对前
给Leonard准备礼物呢？
I don't drive and the only things
available within walking distaenc
我开不来车 那么步行范围内
唯一可行的
are a thai restaurant and a gas station.
就是泰国菜餐馆和加油站
I suppose I could wrap up an order of
mee krob and a coup e of ttery scratchers.
也许我可以带一份米制面条
外加一张即刮彩券
Okay let's do this-- I will
drive sheldon to get a present.
我们这么安排-- 我载
Sheldon去买礼物
And howard, you need to get rid
of leonard for about two hours.
Howard 你得拖住Leonard
大概两个钟头时间
No problem.
没问题
And then, raj, you bring the stuff
across the hall and start setting up.
然后 Raj 你把这些东西
拿到走廊去 把它们装饰好
What if guests show up?
要是客人们来了呢?
Entertain them.
好好招待
What if they're women?
如果是女客人呢?
Stare at them and make
them feel uncomfortable.
死盯她们 弄得她们不自在
- How's it goin'?
- Fine.
- 玩得如何?
- 很好
So listen, the nuart is showing the
revised, definitive cut of blade runner.
我听说 Nuart剧院正在上映
银翼杀手最终剪辑版
Seen it.
看过的
No, you've seen the 25th
anniversary final cut.
不 你看的那是25周年
纪念的最终剪辑版本
This one has eight seconds
of previously unseen footage.
这一次有长达八秒的未公映片段
They say it completely
changes the tone of the film.
他们说 这八秒完全改变了电影的基调
pass.
算了吧
Come on. Afterwards, there's a q &
a with harrison ford's body double.
不是吧 片尾还有
哈里森・福特替身的访谈问答
Look, I'm in the halo
bale of my life here.
你看 我正在到了光晕游戏的
要紧关头
There's this kid in copenhagen--
he has no immune system,
这个哥本哈根的孩子--
没有免疫功能
so all he does is sit in his
bubble and play halo 24-seven.
所以他只好整天坐在防菌隔膜里
玩光晕游戏
Can't you play him some other time?
你就不能改天和他玩吗?
Not if you believe his doctors.
除非你不相信他的医生的话
Oh, my god, do you smell gas?
天啦 你闻到煤气味了吗?
- No.
- Yeah, no.
- 没
- 的确 没有
You know, they have dvds over there.
DVD是在那边的
Yes, but they have
rndvd buers over here.
对 但DVD刻录机在这边的
Leonard needs a dvd burner.
Leonard需要DVD刻录机的
Sheldon, a gift shouldn't be something
someone needs, it should be something fun.
Sheldon 礼物不是满足别人
的需要的 而是充满快乐的东西
You know, something they
wouldn't buy for themself.
是那些 他们不会买给自己的东西
You mean like a sweater?
比如说 毛衣?
It's a fun sweater.
是件充满乐趣的毛衣
It's got a bold geometric print.
上面印有狂野的几何图形
- Is it the geometry that makes it fun?
- Okay...
- 几何图形让它具有了乐趣?
- 好吧...
the point is one of the ways
we show we care about people
最重要的是能让人们
体会到我们的关心
is by putting thought and imagination
into the gifts we give them.
通过礼物传达我们
对他们的美好想法
Okay, I see. So, not a dvd burner.
好吧 我明白了
那就不买刻录机
Exactly.
很正确
Something he wouldn't buy
for himself. Something fun.
他不会给自己买的
能给他带来快乐的东西
Something like... an
802-11n wireless router!
比如... 802-11的无线路由器!
Here you go, copenhagen boy.
该你了 哥本哈根小鬼
How about a taste of hans
christian hand grenade?
试试看德国产的手榴弹滋味如何?
Oh, that could not feel good.
那感觉一定很糟
Come on, come... oh, you clever...
来呀 来呀...你这个机灵...
come on. Come on. Take that!
来 来吧 看我的!
- What's the matter?
- This granola bar, it has peanuts in it!
- 怎么了?
- 这燕麦卷棒 上面有花生粒!
Oh, my god. Why did you eat it?
天啦 为什么你还要吃?
I don't know. It was just there!
我哪知道 它刚好就在那儿!
If I had a gun there, would
you have shot yourself?
如果那儿是把枪 你会崩了自己吗?
Don't yell at me! I've got
to go to the emergency room!
别骂我! 我得去急诊科!
Now?
现在去?
No, after my tongue has swollen
to the size of a brisket!
等我的舌头肿成鸡胸脯那样再去!?
All right, uh, just let me get my keys.
好吧 我去拿钥匙
Oh, god, oh, god, oh, god!
天呀 天呀 天呀...
The laundry is out of the hamper.
衣服已经腾出盥洗篮
Okay, sheldon, what
was it supposed to be?
拜托 Sheldon 你说还能是什么意思?
Fine. It's out of the washer!
好吧 是洗衣机还不行嘛!
I'll call you when it's in the dryer.
等进入烘干机我再给你打电话
All right, let's go.
好了 咱们走
what do you think?
你觉得呢?
Um, that one.
唔 买那个
- Because of the two additional ethernet ports?
- Sure.
- 因为有两个附加的以太网端口?
- 没错
He doesn't need them. He's already
got a six-port ethernet switch.
他不需要 他已经有个6端口转换器了
- Oh, okay, then this one.
- Why?
- 好 那就买这个吧
- 为什么?
I don't know. The man on
the box looks so happy.
我不知道 包装上这男的笑得很开心
Penny, if I'm going to buy leonard
a gift, I'm going to do it right.
Penny 如果我要给Leonard买礼物
我就要买好它
I refuse to let him experience
the same childhood trauma I did.
我不想让他遭受我童年的精神创伤
I know I'm gonna regret
this, but: What trauma?
我知道我会后悔问的
是什么精神创伤?
On my 12th birthday, I really
wanted a titanium centrifuge so,
我12岁生日时
非常想得到一个钛金属离心机
you know, I could separate
radioactive isotopes.
我就能分离放射性同位素了
Of course.
当然
Instead of a titanium centrifuge,
my parents bought me...
我父母没有给我买钛金属离心机
而是...
wow, this is hard.
唉 难以启齿
They got me a motorized dirt bike.
他们给我买了辆机动山地车
No!
不是吧
What 12-year-old boy wants
a motorized dirt bike?
哪个12岁男孩想要机动山地车?
All of them?
每一个
- Really?
- Yeah.
- 真的吗?
- 对呀
Okay, so we're getting this one?
好啦 我们就买这个了?
- Yeah, I suppose.
- All right, let's go.
- 嗯 我想是的
- 很好 咱们走
Exexse me.
打扰一下
Do you know anything about this stuff?
你对这个东西有了解吗?
I know everything about this stuff.
我对这个东西了如指掌
Woman: Okay, I have my own
wholesale flower business
好的 我开了一家鲜花批发店
and I want to hook up my computer in the front
entrance with the one in my refrigerated warehouse.
我想把前台和冷冻仓库的电脑
连接在一起
Here, buy this one: Look, it's the
one we're getting. See? Happy guy.
买这个 我们买的就是这个
看他笑得多开心
No, no, no, she doesn't want that.
不不不 她不能买那个
She needs a point-to-point peer
network with a range extender.
她需要的是有区域扩展功能的点对点网络
Thank you.
谢谢
Which hard drive do I
want-- firewire or usb?
我要买哪个硬件
苹果火线还是USB?
It depends on what
buss you have available.
这取决于你用的什么总线(公交车)了
I drive a chevy cavalier.
我开的是雪弗莱跑车
Oh, dear lord.
上帝啊
- Sheldon, we have to go.
- Not now, penny. This poor man needs me.
- Sheldon 我们得走了
- 现在不行 Penny 这个可怜人需要我
You, hold on. I'll be right with you.
你等等 我一会儿就帮你
What computer do you have?
你的电脑是什么样的?
And please don't say "a white one."
别跟我说"是白色的"
Excuse me.
打扰一下
Fill this out. Have a seat.
填表 坐着等
No, listen. See, we're throwing
my friend a surprise party
不 听着 我们要给朋友
开一个惊喜派对
and I'm supposed to keep him out
of his apartment for two hours.
我得把他骗出公寓两个小时
Fill this out and have a seat.
填表 坐着等
No, see, the only way I could gehit m
to leave was to tell him I ate a peanut
不 你瞧 我骗他离开的唯一办法
就是告诉他我吃了花生
because I'm allergic to peanuts.
因为我对花生过敏
Well, in that case, fill
this out and have a seat.
好 这样的话 填表 坐着等
Look, all I need from you is to take
me in the back and give me a band-aid
拜托 我需要你带我到后面去
给我贴个创可贴
so I can pretend I had
a shot of epinephrine,
我可以假装打了一针肾上腺素
and then you tell my friend you need to keep me
under observation for about an hour, hour and a half.
你可以告诉我朋友 我需要留下观察
一小时 或一个半小时
- Is that all you need?
- Yes.
- 你就想要这个?
- 是的
Get out of my er.
离我远点儿
No, you don't understand.
不 你不明白
Oh, I understand, but unfortunately, this
hospital is not equipped to treat stupid.
我明白 算你倒霉 这医院不给傻子治病
Okay, I get it. I know
how the world works.
好吧 我懂了 我知道这社会怎么回事儿
How about if I were to introduce to
you to the man who freed your people?
我给你一位解放了你们同胞的人怎么样?
(林肯解放了黑奴 5美元钞票上有他的头像)
Unless my people were freed by benjamin
franklin and his five twin brothers,
除非我的同胞是富兰克林(100美元钞票上头像)
和他的五个孪生兄弟解放的
you are wasting your time.
你在浪费时间
Hey, sorry, I couldn't find a
parking spot. How are you doing?
对不起 我一直没找到停车位 你怎么样了?
Bad, very bad.
糟糕 非常糟糕
Really? You don't look like
you're swelling up at all.
真的吗? 你看上去一点都不肿啊
Maybe we should just pick up some
benadryl at the drugstore and go home.
或许我们应该去药店
买些抗组织胺药然后回家
- We can't go home.
- Why not?
- 我们不能回家
- 为什么不能?
Because...
因为...
because...
brisket! Brisket!
鸡胸脯! 鸡胸脯!
Water! Need water!
水! 我要喝水!
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
penny, listen, I've got a problem.
Penny 听着 我有麻烦了
Yeah, well, so do I. Look, you
gotta stall leonard a little longer.
唔 我也是 你得多拖住Leonard一会儿
I don't think I can.
我想我做不到
You have to. We all have to be there
at the same time to yell surprise.
必须做到 我们要同时到给他个惊喜
Okay, you have to understand something.
你要了解情况
We're in a hospital right now.
我们现在在医院
Why? Is leonard okay?
为什么? Leonard还好吗?
Leonard's fine. I'm fine.
Leonard很好 我很好
Thanks for asking, by the way.
谢谢你关心 顺便说一声
Okay, I don't need your attitude.
你别发脾气
Listen, just hold him
there a little longer.
听着 再多拖住他一会儿
Look, I've done my best, but he wants to
go home and I don't know how to stop him.
我已经尽力了 他想回家
我不知如何阻止他
Okay, how about this?
这个建议怎样?
You keep himhere a little longer,
and when you get to the party,
你多拖住他一会儿
等你到了派对上
I'll point out which
of my friends are easy?
我会告诉你 我朋友里哪个比较随便
Don't toy with me, woman.
别耍我啊 丫头
I got a hot former fat
girl with no self-esteem,
我认识一个减肥成功
而且没有自尊的辣妹
I got a girl who punishes
her father by sleeping around
和一个为了惩罚她爸爸
而和别人乱搞的女孩
and alcoholic who's two tequila shots
away from letting you wear her like a hat.
还有一个酒鬼妹
在两杯龙舌兰下肚后任你摆布
Thy will be done.
我会搞定的
I'm doing this for you, little buddy.
我可是为了你才做的 小伙计
Okay, we don't have that in stock...
我们现在没有存货...
but I can special-order it for you.
不过可以为你专门预定
Him.
就是他
Excuse me, sir. You don't work here.
对不起先生 你不在这里工作
Yes, well, apparently,
neither does anyone else.
没错 显然没人在这里工作
- Eldon, we have to go.
- Why?
- Sheldon 我们得走了
- 为什么?
Well, for one thing, we're late
for leonard's birthday party,
第一 Leonard的派对我们要迟到了
and for another, I told
him to call security.
第二 我让他去叫保安了
Good luck.
祝你好运
By the way, a six-year-old
could hack your computer system.
顺便说一下 6岁孩子都能黑了你的电脑
Keep walking.
快走
"1234" is not a secure password.
1234做密码可不安全
Excuse me-- my friend is having
an allergic reaction to peanuts.
对不起 我朋友对花生过敏了
- No, he's not.
- Yes, he is.
- 不 他没有
- 他真的过敏了
Look, sir, we are very
busy here, and I...
先生 我们很忙 我...
holy crap!
我的妈呀!
Please help me!
请救救我!
Code four! I need a gurney!
急救! 这里需要担架!
- Right away! Right away!
- Thank you.
- 在这里 在这里
- 谢谢你
Say what you will about the
healthcare system in this country,
虽然你对医疗体系充满期待
but when they're afraid
of lawsuits, *********
可他们怕吃官司
还是会做系统的检查
I really don't think the
colonoscopy was necessary.
结肠镜检查真没必要
You know, before you got all swollen up,
要知道 在你肿起来之前
I actually thought you were trying
to keep me out of the apartment
我以为你要骗我出公寓
so you could throw me a surprise party.
好为我开一个惊喜派对
Oh, right, it's your birthday.
也是哦 今天是你生日
I had no idea it was your
birthday. I completely forgot.
我不知道是你生日 我完全忘记了
Wow, what a lousy way to spend a
birthday. Well, it's all over now.
这个生日过得太糟了 现在全都完了
There is a party, isn't there?
确实有派对 是吗?
Maybe.
可能吧
Howard?
Are you mad?
你生气了?
How could I be mad?
我怎么会生气呢?
You actually risked your life
because you care about me.
你可是冒了生命危险
因为你关心我
Yeah, that's why I did it.
对 所以我才这么做的
All right. Here we go.
好的 咱们瞧瞧
My first birthday party.
我第一个生日派对
* I see your true colors *
* 我看到了你的本色 *
* and that's why I love you.*
* 这就是为什么我爱你 *
Dude, everybody left an hour ago.
兄弟 大家一小时前就走了
Surprise!
惊喜!
******* I am on your birthday party.
快看 Leonard 我在你的生日派对上
I don't know where you are,
dude, but it's really kick-ass!
我不知道你在哪儿 哥们儿
这个派对棒呆了!
Everyone is very, very drunk and...
每个人都喝得很醉很醉 而且...
oh, and look, there's a
girl taking her shirt off!
快看 那个女孩把上衣脱了!
That's my friend carol.
她是我朋友Carol
Remind me-- I gotta
introduce her to howard.
差点忘了 我要把她介绍给Howard
Oh, sweet krishna,
shake that rupee maker!
亲爱的克利须那神啊!
快摇起你那宝贝来!
I'm so sorry you didn't get your party.
对不起 你没赶上自己的派对
Oh, it's okay.
没关系
Well, happy birthday, anyways.
不管怎样 还是祝你生日快乐
Hey, penny, wh-wh-when's
your birthday?
Penny 你什么时候过生日?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
--------------------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------------------
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: lauracai 王泳东 MiaT
校对: 欧屁屁
时间轴: 咔肉肉